echineselearning.com 2007-12-24

# Learn Chinese Online, One-on-One Chinese Learning, Privacy Policy - eChineseLearning

eChineseLearning is committed to protecting your privacy when you visit our web site. We want you to know what information we collect when you visit us, how we use that information, and how you can update it. eChineseLearning reserves the right to append or otherwise modify this Privacy Statement at any time, so please re-visit this page occasionally to check for updates.  

Information Collected Automatically  
  
The types of information your browser or internet session automatically sends us each time you visit our site, which we automatically collect, includes: 

  * Your browser, e.g., Internet Explorer, Netscape Navigator. 
  * Your Internet domain, e.g., AOL, Netcom, EarthLink, etc. 
  * You computer's operating system, e.g., Windows, Macintosh, UNIX, Linux. 
  * Your navigation path, i.e., the URLs of where you come to our site from, which of our pages you visit, and where you go as your leave. 
  * Your IP address. 

This information lets us see how users are finding our sites, and it tells us which pages are visited the most often so we can make our web sites more useful.  

Your Personal Profile  
  
When we ask information of you, our primary interest is to provide you with more personalized service. We do not sell, rent or trade your name or personal details to other organizations unless you give us your permission to do so. You can always opt out of these service by simply updating your personal profile.   
You have the ability to change or update your personal information at any time. You can do this by going to your personal profile. Just login and click "My Account ".  

Security Measures  
We also insist on password verification at sign-in to protect against unauthorized access to your personal profile and course history. If you leave the computer unattended without logging out of the site, we log you out automatically after some time has passed.  
   
Registration For A Subscription And Payment Security  
eChineseLearning offers Chinese language courses online. To take one of these courses, you need to become a member of eChineseLearning.

You also need to supply us with credit card information so that you can pay for the service you request. This information is encrypted on a secure server by PayPal, the world-wide recognized online payment system.  

Cookies  
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that we store on your computer's browser or hard drive. We use cookies to customize the site for your country and language. Our cookies do not collect additional information from your computer's browser or hard drive. Most browsers allow you the option of preventing cookies from being stored on your computer, though doing so will cause you to lose many of the benefits of eChineseLearning.

You may be given cookies from our advertisers on our co-branded sites. We do not control, nor do we have access to any of the information they may collect.  

IP Addresses And Browser Type  
This site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that eChineseLearning is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of any website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by the eChineseLearning website.   
   
The eChineseLearning privacy policy is subject to change. If we decide to change the way we collect, use or share information, we will take commercially reasonable steps to notify members by way of an email that explains the changes and gives them the choice as to whether or not we may use their information in the new manner. If you have any questions about this policy statement, or about any of eChineseLearning's other policies and practices, please contact us.
